<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Script><Phase><Text>I would like to talk about where you live. Talk about your favorite room in your home. why do you like that room? What do you normally do there?</Text><Convtext></Convtext><Starttime>0</Starttime><Category>true</Category></Phase><Phase><Text>As I've mentioned, my family lives in an apartment in the northern part of Seoul, in an area called Seong-buk gu.</Text><Convtext>앞서 말했듯이, 우리 가족은 서울 강북에 위치한 성북동이라는 지역에 있는 한 아파트에 살고 있습니다.</Convtext><Starttime>13051</Starttime><Category>false</Category></Phase><Phase><Text>We live on the 12th floor of a 15-story building. </Text><Convtext>15층 아파트인데 우리 가족은 12층에서 삽니다.</Convtext><Starttime>19535</Starttime><Category>false</Category></Phase><Phase><Text>We are fortunate enough to have a view of the city on one side of the apartment and a breathtaking view of the mountains on the other.</Text><Convtext>저희가 사는 집 한쪽으로는 도시 전경이 내려다 보이고, 다른 한 쪽으로는 아름다운 산이 펼쳐져 보입니다.</Convtext><Starttime>23407</Starttime><Category>false</Category></Phase><Phase><Text>My favorite room in my home has got to be my study.</Text><Convtext>집에서 제가 가장 좋아하는 공간은 서재입니다.</Convtext><Starttime>30845</Starttime><Category>false</Category></Phase><Phase><Text>It has a large window that takes in the view of the mountains perfectly.</Text><Convtext>큰 창이 있어서 산이 한눈에 내려다보입니다.</Convtext><Starttime>34209</Starttime><Category>false</Category></Phase><Phase><Text>My desk faces the window, so when I'm a bit stressed I can just look out at the stunning landscape and take a deep breath.</Text><Convtext>책상은 창문을 마주하고 있어서 스트레스를 받을 때에는 멋진 자연 경관을 내다보며 심호흡을 할 수 있지요.</Convtext><Starttime>38619</Starttime><Category>false</Category></Phase><Phase><Text>This feature of the study helps me stay productive, even on days when I don't feel like working.</Text><Convtext>서재의 이런 장점 덕분에 의욕이 나지 않는 날에도 힘을 낼 수 있습니다.</Convtext><Starttime>46229</Starttime><Category>false</Category></Phase><Phase><Text>It's also the room I go to when I need to have some time of my own after playing with the kids.</Text><Convtext>아이들과 놀아준 후에 혼자만의 시간을 가지고 싶을 때 찾는 공간이 서재이기도 합니다.</Convtext><Starttime>52265</Starttime><Category>false</Category></Phase></Script>