<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Script><Phase><Text>Tell me about some activities you do at home. What do you do in the morning and what do you do in the evening? Tell me all about what you do at home.</Text><Convtext></Convtext><Starttime>0</Starttime><Category>true</Category></Phase><Phase><Text>I have to say that I'm a morning person.</Text><Convtext>저는 아침형 인간입니다.</Convtext><Starttime>12293</Starttime><Category>false</Category></Phase><Phase><Text>Ihave a lot of energy when I wake up, </Text><Convtext>잠에서 깨면 의욕이 넘칩니다.</Convtext><Starttime>15419</Starttime><Category>false</Category></Phase><Phase><Text>so I like to go on the treadmill for about 20minutes before doing some light weight training for about 15 minutes.</Text><Convtext>그래서 러닝 머신에서 20분간 운동을 하고, 근력 운동을 15분 정도 합니다.</Convtext><Starttime>17344</Starttime><Category>false</Category></Phase><Phase><Text>Although doing this in the morning means that I have to get up earlier than I would otherwise ned to, I think it's worth keeping in shape.</Text><Convtext>운동하려면 그렇지 않을 때와 비교해서 아침에 더 일찍 일어나야 하지만, 저는 건강 관리가 중요하다고 생각합니다.</Convtext><Starttime>24072</Starttime><Category>false</Category></Phase><Phase><Text>After I finish my workout, I don't have time to do anything but take a quick shower, grab a bite, and leave for work.</Text><Convtext>운동을 마친 후에는 샤워를 빨리하고 간단히 아침을 먹고 출근을 합니다.</Convtext><Starttime>32084</Starttime><Category>false</Category></Phase><Phase><Text>Evening times are a bit unpredictable.</Text><Convtext>저녁 시간 일정은 그때 그때 다릅니다.</Convtext><Starttime>39085</Starttime><Category>false</Category></Phase><Phase><Text>Depending on what time I get home from the office, the kids are either wide awake or fast asleep.</Text><Convtext>퇴근에서 집에 도착하는 시간이 이르면 아이들이 깨어있지만 그렇지 않으면 이미 곤히 잠들어 있지요.</Convtext><Starttime>41804</Starttime><Category>false</Category></Phase><Phase><Text>If they're awake I play with them for a while.</Text><Convtext>아이들이 깨어있는 경우 저는 잠시라도 아이들과 시간을 보냅니다.</Convtext><Starttime>48020</Starttime><Category>false</Category></Phase><Phase><Text>If not, my wife and I just talk about how the day went and go to sleep.</Text><Convtext>그렇지 않을 때는 아내와 그 날 있었던 일에 대해서 이야기하다가 잠자리에 듭니다.</Convtext><Starttime>51088</Starttime><Category>false</Category></Phase><Phase><Text>I normally go to bed at midnight.</Text><Convtext>보통 저는 자정에 잠자리에 듭니다. </Convtext><Starttime>56393</Starttime><Category>false</Category></Phase></Script>